Cecilia White

USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER

Virginia, USA | 804-396-1849 | ceciliawhite002@gmail.com

Summary

Dedicated designer with a passion for technology and its role in everyday life. I create spaces that allow users to operate their devices more efficiently and effectively. In my work I put users' needs and frustrations first to curate a product that benefits both producers and consumers. Using my UX skills I create an effortless experience that fosters positive interactions between end users and products.

Experience

ieiMedia | Interactive Designer

June 2023 - July 2023

- Compiled stories, photographs, and films into a cohesive interactive webpage
- Collaborated with a team of 6 designers to curate an immersive web experience
- Assisted team members with video and photo production
- Interviewed and built rapport with article sources

James Madison University | Interactive Designer

January 2023 - May 2023

- Developed and designed a mobile application starting from ideation and ending with prototyping
- Conducted user research to understand and empathize with users
- Created low and high fidelity prototypes using Figma
- Compiled findings into a concise final report detailing the project from start to finish

SingleStone Consulting | Marketing Intern

June 2021 - August 2021

- Participated in foundational agile and scrum training in a team environment
- Synthesized company blogs and created visuals graphics for social media and website
- Managed website presence for employee page using WordPress

Education

James Madison University, Harrisonburg Virginia

Bachelor of Arts in Media Arts and Design – Interactive Design Concentration

May 2024

Minor: Communications

Cumulative GPA: 3.6

Dean's List: Fall 2021, Spring 2022, Fall 2022, Spring 2023

International Experience: Interactive Design Study Abroad Program in Urbino, Italy

Skills

- UX/UI
- Visual Design
- Prototyping
- Wireframing
- Figma
- Storyboarding
- User Flows
- User Research

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- WordPress
- Adobe Creative Cloud
- Microsoft Office Suite